Guide to the Archives Foreign File (AFF), Section 1
Archives Foreign File (AFF), Section 1
- Box: 16, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Item 13: News-Sheet, 1983; Publication (Box 16, Folder 1)
    Notes: no.19 (1983:Feb.)
  - Item 14: News-Sheet, 1985; Publication (Box 16, Folder 1)
    Notes: no.23 (1985:Aug.)
  - Item 15: An Introduction to Astronomy, 1979; Publication (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Item 16: APEX: Education, 1979; Publication (Box 16, Folder 1)
    Author: Association of Professional, Executive, Clerical & Computer Staff
  - Item 17: APEX: Legal Advice Scheme, Publication (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Item 18: Fine Art, Art Appreciation, Flower Arrangement, Craft, 1979; Publication (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Item 19: News-Sheet, 1988; Publication (Box 16, Folder 1)
    Notes: no.8 (1988:Jan.)
  - Item 20: News-Sheet, 1981; Publication (Box 16, Folder 1)
    Notes: no.16 (1981:Aug.)
  - Item 21: Part-Time Study with the School of Continuing Education, 1979; Publication (Box 16, Folder 1)
    Author: University of Kent at Canterbury
  - Item 22: Day Release Courses in CommunicationsIndustrial Relations, 1978; Publication (Box 16, Folder 1)
    Author: Universtiy College of Swansea
  - Item 23: Education Scheme 1978, Publication (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Item 24: Psychology, Politics, Economics, Sociology, Law, Navigation, First Aid, 1979; Publication (Box 16, Folder 1)
    Author: Oxford College of Further Education
  - Item 25: A Day Release Course for Men and Women in Industry, 1979; Publication (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Item 26: Managers and Professional Staff in APEX, Publication (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Item 27: Professional and Executive Staff Have a Lot to Think About, Publication (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Item 28: Report of a Court of Inquiry Under the RT HonComputer Staff, 1977; Publication (Box 16, Folder 1)
    Author: Association of Professional, Executive, Clerical and Computer Staff; Grunwick (Firm)
  - Item 29: A Load of Bullshit: Report of a Committee inquiringClaimants Unions, Publication (Box 16, Folder 1)
    Author: National Federation of Claimants Unions
  - Item 30: Claimants Handbook for Strikers, Publication (Box 16, Folder 1)
    Author: Claimants Unions
  - Item 31: Unsupported Mothers Handbook, Publication (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Box: 16, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Handbook of Agreements, Publication (Box 16, Folder 2)
    Author: British Leyland UK Limited, Leyland Cars
    Notes: contents of a binder, misc.
- Box: 16, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: National Joint Apprenticeship SchemeApprenticeship Agreement, 1952; Publication (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: National Joint Apprenticeship SchemeApprenticeship Agreement, 1952; Publication (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Annual Conference - 1977 SupplementaryIndustrial Democracy, Publication (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Annual Conference - 1978 SupplementaryThe Economy in 1977, Publication (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Annual General Meeting 1978 SundayPalatine Road, Manchester, Publication (Box 16, Folder 3)
    Author: Society for Industrial Tutors
  - Item 6: Annual General Meeting 1978: Agenda, Publication (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: Annual General Meeting 1981 SundayPalatine Road, Manchester, Publication (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: Annual Report 1977/78, 1978; Publication (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: APEX Education - General Accident Section, Publication (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Item 10: APEX Education Programme, Publication (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Item 11: Association of ProfessionalStaff (correspondence: Nash-Handley), 1978; Publication (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Item 12: British Labor Educators, Industrial Tutors Build Active Association, Publication (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Item 13: Constitution, Publication (Box 16, Folder 3)
    Author: Society of Industrial Turtors
  - Item 14: Constitution and Standing Orders to govern biennial conferences, 1975; Publication (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Item 15: Dealing with Redundancies: Checklist, 1978; Publication (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Item 16: Industrial Relations in Local Government, 1979; Publication (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Item 17: Notes of Meeting Held at Central Depot at 3:20 PM Thursday1978, Publication (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Item 18: One Week Residential School on Industrial Relations, 1978; Publication (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Item 19: Partial Alteration to Rules of the Associationfor the years shown, 1977; Publication (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Item 20: Priority Work, 1974-1977, Publication (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Item 21: S.I.T. Evidence Sub-Committee, 1978; Publication (Box 16, Folder 3)
    Author: Society of Industiral Tutors
  - Item 22: Society of Industrial Tutors: Minutes of the 9th Annual General Meeting, 1977; Publication (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Item 23: Society of Industrial Tutors: The Aims of the Society, Publication (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Item 24: Syllabuses and Timetable for a One YearStanton and Staveley, 1978; Publication (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Item 25: Syllabuses and Timetable for a Two Yearin the Mining Industry, 1978; Publication (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Item 26: Topics: Collective Bargaining 1977/78, 1978; Publication (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Item 27: Topics: Health, Saftey and Welfare, 1978; Publication (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Item 28: Union Summer School, 1978; Publication (Box 16, Folder 3)
    Notes: class list
  - Item 29: WEA Class, Subject: Industrial Democracy, Publication (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Item 30: WEA Classes in Berkshire Autumn 1978, Publication (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Item 31: WEA, Oxford Branch: Courses for Adults, Programme 1978/79, 1979; Publication (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Item 32: Women's Rights, Publication (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Item 33: Workers' Educational Association, Wythenshawe Branch: 1978-79 Season, 1979; Publication (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Item 34: Case Study, Information Agreements, Publication (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Item 35: Case Study, Information Agreements, 1978; Publication (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Item 36: All in a Year's Work: A WEA Response to Unemployment 1981/82, 1982; Publication (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Item 37: Association of Professional, Executive, Clerical and Computer Staff, Publication (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Item 38: Association of Professional, Executive, Clerical and Computer Staff, Publication (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Item 39: Trade Unionists and the Workers' Educational Association, Publication (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Box: 16, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The Union, Its Work and Problems: How to Study the Course, Publication (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: The Union, Its Work and Problems: Loan of Books, 1953; Publication (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: The Union, Its Work and Problems: Loan of Books, 1953; Publication (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: The Union, Its Work and Problems: Part II - StructureMembership, Publication (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: The Winning Hand for a Better Deal: USDAW LeafletsHelp Others, 1978; Publication (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: Home Study Course: Introducing USDAW Part IV: The Union at work: Wages and Conditions, Publication (Box 16, Folder 4)
    Notes: pt. IV of a six part home schooling course
  - Item 7: Home Study Course: Introducing USDAW Part Vfor its Members, Publication (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: Day Release Courses in Economics, Industrial RelationsPolitics, 1978; Publication (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Item 9: Day Release Courses in the Standard of Living, the SocialRelations, 1978; Publication (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Item 10: Handbook of National Agreements, 1975; Publication (Box 16, Folder 4)
    Author: Engineering Employers' Federation
  - Item 11: Home Study Course: Introducing USDAW, Worksheetand Politics, Publication (Box 16, Folder 4)
    Author: Union Shop, Distributive and Allied Workers (Great Britain)
  - Item 12: Home Study Course: Introducing USDAW, WorksheetDevelopment, Publication (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Item 13: Home Study Course: Introducing USDAW, Worksheetof the Union, Publication (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Item 14: Home Study Course: Introducing USDAW, WorksheetTrade Unionism, Publication (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Item 15: Pay and Conditions Agreement 1 November 198, 1982; Publication (Box 16, Folder 4)
    Author: Austin Rover Group; Jaguar Cars Ltd.; Unipart Group of Companies; BL Technology
  - Item 16: Union of Shop, Distributive and Allied Workers: Rules, 1977; Publication (Box 16, Folder 4)
    Author: Union of Shop, Distributive and Allied Workers
  - Item 17: Rules (Parts 1 and 1a) adopted by the Rules Revision Meeting 1975, Publication (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Item 18: Productivity and Productivity Deals, 1971; Publication (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Item 19: Education and Training, Publication (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Item 20: Now available: British Labour Struggles 1727-1850, 1974; Publication (Box 16, Folder 4)
    Notes: catalog of books
- Box: 16, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Newsletter of the Democratic Left (February 1976 - Vol. IV, No. 2), Publication (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: The Bloody Worker: Britain's Fall Guy, 1971; Publication (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Trade Union Studies Journal Autumn 1981, Publication (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Barbara Waves Her Muleta, 1970; Publication (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Ken Coates (Betrand Russell Foundation), 1975; Publication (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: Leyland Cars Revised British LeylandSummary of Amendments, 1976; Publication (Box 16, Folder 5)
    Author: British Leyland Motor Corporation
  - Item 7: Society of Industrial Tutors (general letter), 1980; Publication (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Item 8: The Passing of the British Working Class, Publication (Box 16, Folder 5)
    Author: Dom Moraes
  - Item 9: Agreement on Terms and ConditionsUnion of Engineering Workers, 1985; Publication (Box 16, Folder 5)
    Author: Nissan Manufacturing Ltd.
  - Item 10: Annual Report 1979/80, 1980; Publication (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Item 11: News-Sheet Supplement No. 1 (August 1980), Publication (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Item 12: One-Day Workshop - PEL Research Project, 1980; Publication (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Item 13: Minutes of the Eleventh Annual General Meeting, 1979; Publication (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Item 14: Period 1: Protest Literature of the Industrial Revolution (1794-1867), Publication (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Item 15: Period 1: Protest Literature of the Industrial Revolution dating from 1794 to 1881, Publication (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Item 16: Defend Your Unions!, 1982; Publication (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Box: 16, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Rule 11(b)(i) - Sliding Scale Clause and Index of Retail Prices, 1957; Publication (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Promulgation of Constitutional AmendmentsWorking Rule 5A, 1957; Publication (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Promulgation of Constitutional AmendmentsWorking Rule 5A, 1957; Publication (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: Factpacks No. 11: The General Strike - Living History, 1988; Publication (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: Factpacks No. 7: Early Trade Unions (to 1914) - Living History, 1988; Publication (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Box: 16, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: (Table T21/T22, page 200/201 - source unknown), Publication (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Annual Report: Berks, Bucks and Oxon District 1975/76, 1976; Publication (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: Cooperative Learning in Discussion Groups, Publication (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: Disclosure of Information: Financial Information for Trade Unionists, Publication (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: Form for Evaluation of Instructor, 1978; Publication (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Item 6: Handling Grievances: Discipline Cases, Interviewing Exercise, Publication (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Item 7: Industrial Relations: Miners Day Release, Year I, Publication (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Item 8: Legal Aspects of Employment: Contracts and Dismissals, 1976; Publication (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Item 9: Management Brief, Publication (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Item 10: Mrs. Glynn's Dressmaking Class (pg. 82 - source unknown), Publication (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Item 11: Paid Educational Leave Research Project, Publication (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Item 12: Questionnaire to Evaluate Lectures (source unknown), Publication (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Item 13: Raleigh Apprentices Course, 1975; Publication (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Item 14: Safety Representatives: Shop Floor Organisation for Health and Safety, 1978; Publication (Box 16, Folder 7)
    Author: Workers' Educaitonal Associaiton
  - Item 15: Syllabuses and Timetable for a One Year DayCommunications, 1978; Publication (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Item 16: Syllabuses and Timetable for a One Year DayIndustrial Relations, 1978; Publication (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Item 17: The Woodwork Class (source unknown), Publication (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Item 18: Trade Union Studies Journal Spring 1981, Publication (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Item 19: Union Brief, Publication (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Item 20: Universities Council for Adult Education Report on Industrial Studies, 1976; Publication (Box 16, Folder 7)
    Author: Universities Council for Adult Education (Great Britain)
  - Item 21: WEA Industrial Branch programme 1977/78, 1978; Publication (Box 16, Folder 7)
    Notes: programme
  - Item 22: Workshop Negotiation: A Role Playing Exercise, Publication (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Item 23: Annual Report 1980/81, 1981; Publication (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Item 24: New From Socialists Unlimited: Pamphlets, badgesfor socialism, 1980; Publication (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Box: 16, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Trade Union Research Unit Rules, 1973; Publication (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: A Better Future for Defense Jobs: A TGWU Strategy for Arms Conversion, 1983; Publication (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Beware of Imitations!, 1977; Publication (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: Draft Agenda for 1972 Congress, 1971; Publication (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: Education and the Working Class, Ruskin College 1899-1909, 1977; Publication (Box 16, Folder 8)
    Author: Paul Yorke
  - Item 6: Home Study Course: Introducing USDAW Part I: The Essence of Trade Unionism, Publication (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Item 7: Home Study Course: Introducing USDAW Part II: The Union's growth and Development, Publication (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Item 8: Home Study Course: Introducing USDAW Part III: The Structure, Government and Administration of the Union, Publication (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Item 9: Home Study Course: Introducing USDAW, Worksheetfor its Members, Publication (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Item 10: Industrial Democracy: Interim Report by the TUC General Council, 1973; Publication (Box 16, Folder 8)
    Author: Trades Union Congress (Great Britain) General Council
  - Item 11: Industrial Relations Summer School 1978, Publication (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Item 12: Lets Face It: Administrative Staff Need an Identity, Publication (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Item 13: News-Sheet, 1985; Publication (Box 16, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.22 (1985:Apr.)
  - Item 14: News-Sheet, 1982; Publication (Box 16, Folder 8)
    Notes: Supplement no.3 (1982:Feb.)
  - Item 15: Publications to Date, 1978; Publication (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Item 16: Ruskin College and Workers Education - A Background Note, 1976; Publication (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Item 17: Ruskin College Partners' Weekend, 1978; Publication (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Item 18: Ruskin Diploma in Development Studies July 1973, Publication (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Item 19: Ruskin History Workshop 12: In Our Time - Britain 1945-1978, Publication (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Item 20: Ruskin Students' Union: Agenda, 1978; Publication (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Item 21: Ruskin Students' Union: Standing Orders, 1978; Publication (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Item 22: TUC Disputes, Principles and Procedures, 1976; Publication (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Item 23: WEA 75-77: Report of the National Committeefor 1975-7, 1977; Publication (Box 16, Folder 8)
    Author: Workers' Educaitonal Association. National Committee
  - Item 24: Home Study Course: Introducing USDAW Part VI The Union and Politics, Publication (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Item 25: Home Study Course: Introducing USDAW, Worksheetand Conditions, Publication (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Box: 16, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Form Design and Control, Publication (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: Report Containing Proposals for the Structure of the Joint International and suggested voting procedures for the Joint Congress, Publication (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: Work Simplification in the Office, Publication (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: Work Study, Publication (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Box: 16, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Social and Labour Legislation in Greece, 1948; Publication (Box 16, Folder 10)
    Author: A.A. Pallis
  - Item 2: The Greek Trade Unions Question, 1949; Publication (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Box: 16, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Adiestramiento del Supervisor Industrial, 1957; Publication (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Item 2: Adiestramiento del Supervisor Industrial: Seccion XI, Publication (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Item 3: Adiestramiento del Supervisor Industrial: Seccion XII, Publication (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Item 4: Adiestramiento Hotelero, 1957; Publication (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Item 5: Fundamentos de la Educacion Vocacional, 1957; Publication (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Item 6: Informacion Para Estudiantes, Maestros y Padres de Familia, 1957; Publication (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Box: 16, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Derechos Y Acciones de Los Empledos y Trabajadores del Estado, 1950; Publication (Box 16, Folder 12)
    Author: Julio Antonio Reyes Cardona
  - Item 2: Estatuto Agrario: Emitido por el Gobierno de la Republica, 1956; Publication (Box 16, Folder 12)
    Author: Guatemala
  - Item 3: Normas de Derecho Vacacional en Guatemala, 1965; Publication (Box 16, Folder 12)
    Author: Emilio Zebadua Garcia
  - Item 4: Organizacion de los Tribunales de TrabajoSistemas de Mexico y Chile, 1951; Publication (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Item 5: Organizacion de los Tribunales de TrabajoSistemas de Mexico y Chile, 1951; Publication (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Item 6: Pacto Colectivo de Condiciones de Trabajo, 1963; Publication (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Item 7: Pacto Colectivo de Condiciones de Trabajo, 1963; Publication (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Item 8: Pacto Colectivo de Condiciones de TrabajoCerveceria Centroamericana, 1959; Publication (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Item 9: Pacto Colectivo de Condiciones de TrabajoElectrica de Guatemala, 1962; Publication (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Item 10: Pacto Colectivo de Condiciones de TrabajoElectrica de Guatemala, 1962; Publication (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Item 11: Pacto Colectivo de Condiciones de TrabajoEmpleados Particulares, 1964; Publication (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Item 12: Sindicato de Luz y Fuerza, 1964; Publication (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Box: 16, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Boletin No. 2, 1957; Publication (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Item 2: Guatemala: Excerpts from 'The Great Fear in Latin America', Publication (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Item 3: Sindicato de Trabajadores del Creditode Guatemala 'S.T.C.', 1965; Publication (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Box: 16, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Africa's Top Nationalist - Or Africa's Prima Donna?, 1967; Publication (Box 16, Folder 14)
    Author: Lloyd Garrison
- Box: 16, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: The Terror in Haiti, 1963; Publication (Box 16, Folder 15)
    Author: Ernest Dale
- Box: 16, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Algunos Hechos Historigos en el Caso de Honduras y Nicaragua, 1958; Publication (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Item 2: Contrato Colectivo de Trabajo Celebrado entre la Tela Railroad Company y el Sindicato de Trabajadores de la Tela Railroad Company, 1966; Publication (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Item 3: Contrato Colectivo de Trabajo Celebrado entre la Tela Railroad Company y el Sindicato de Trabajadores de la Tela Railroad Company, 1966; Publication (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Item 4: Prorroga Del Contrato Colectivo de Trabajo celebrado entre la Tela Railroad Company y el Sindicato de Trabajadores de la Tela Railroad Company, 1964; Publication (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Item 5: Sitraterco Informa, 1957; Publication (Box 16, Folder 16)
- Box: 16, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: A General Review of Hong Kong Labour Movement, 1950; Publication (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Item 2: Trade union education series -- A Guide to Simple Trade Union Accounting, Publication (Box 16, Folder 17)
    Author: Hong Kong. Labour Dept.
  - Item 3: A Short Guide to the Trade Union Registration(Ordinance 52 of 1961), Publication (Box 16, Folder 17)
    Author: Hong Kong. Registry of Trade Unions
  - Item 4: Annual Departmental Reports 1955-6, 1956; Publication (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Item 5: Trade union education series -- How to Strengthen Trade Union, Publication (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Item 6: Trade union education series -- Model Rules for a Welfare Benefit Fund: Sickness, Accident and Death, 1961; Publication (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Item 7: Trade union education series -- Model Rules for Trade Unions, 1961; Publication (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Item 8: Trade union education series -- Simple Trade Union Administration: Part 1. Duties of Officers, Publication (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Item 9: Trade union education series -- Simple Trade Union Administration: Part 2. Conduct of Meetings, Publication (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Item 10: Trade union education series --Simple Trade Union Administration: Part 3. Duties of Members, Publication (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Item 11: Trade union education series -- Simple Trade Union Administration: Part 4. VotingTrade Unions, Publication (Box 16, Folder 17)
- Box: 16, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Hungarian Press Survey No. 1877: The Hungarian Gazette, 8 Oct. 1967, 1968; Publication (Box 16, Folder 18)
    Author: Radio Free Europe
  - Item 2: Hungarian Press Survey No. 1879: The Hungarian Gazette, 8 Oct. 1967, 1968; Publication (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Item 3: Hungarian Press Survey No. 1892: The Hungarian Gazette, 8 Oct. 1967, Publication (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Item 4: Hungarian Press Survey No. 1900: The Hungarian Gazette, 8 Oct. 1967, 1968; Publication (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Item 5: Hungarian Press Survey No. 1901: The Hungarian Gazette, 8 Oct. 1967, 1968; Publication (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Item 6: Hungarian Press Survey No. 1902: The Hungarian Gazette, 8 Oct. 1967, 1968; Publication (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Item 7: Hungarian Press Survey No. 1904: The Hungarian Gazette, 8 Oct. 1967, 1968; Publication (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Item 8: Hungarian Press Survey No. 1906: The Hungarian Gazette, 8 Oct. 1967, 1968; Publication (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Item 9: Hungarian Press Survey No. 1907: The Hungarian Gazette, 8 Oct. 1967, 1968; Publication (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Item 10: Mondo Economico (several articles) (14 Settembre 1957), Publication (Box 16, Folder 18)
    Author: Instituto per gli studi di economia
  - Item 11: The Characteristic Features of the New Hungarian Labor Code, 1968; Publication (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Item 12: The Hungarian Labor Code in Perspective: The Collective Contract, 1968; Publication (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Item 13: The Relations of the American and the Americo-HungarianErvin Szabo, 1963; Publication (Box 16, Folder 18)
    Author: Janos Jemnitz
  - Item 14: Trade Union News from Hungary No. 2, 1949; Publication (Box 16, Folder 18)
    Author: Hungarian News and Information Service
    Notes: no.2
  - Item 15: Trade Union News from Hungary No. 3, 1949; Publication (Box 16, Folder 18)
    Notes: no.3